filetut.com 2018-11-16

# Filetut Storage - Manera facil de compartir sus archivos

  * ### The Filetut Privacy Policy was updated on September 01, 2014. 

#### Your privacy is important to Filetut. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.  

#### 

#####  California Do Not Track Disclosure | Information Regarding Commercial Electronic Messages in Canada  
Collection and Use of Personal Information  
Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.  
You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Filetut or an Filetut affiliated company. Filetut and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any queries you may have. 

Here are some examples of the types of personal information Filetut may collect and how we may use it.  
What personal information we collect

When you create an Filetut ID, apply for commercial credit, purchase a product, download a software update, register for a class at an Filetut Retail Store, contact us or participate in an online survey, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information.  
When you share your content with family and friends using Filetut products, send gift certificates and products, or invite others to participate in Filetut services or forums, Filetut may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number. Filetut will use such information to fulfill your requests, provide the relevant product or service, or for anti-fraud purposes.  
In the U.S., we may ask for a government issued ID in limited circumstances including when setting up a wireless account and activating your device, for the purpose of extending commercial credit, managing reservations, or as required by law.

How we use your personal information  
The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Filetut’s latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating your preferences.  
We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our products, services, content and advertising, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes.  
We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. For example, we may use date of birth to determine the age of Filetut ID account holders.  
From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with Filetut, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.  
We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Filetut’s products, services, and customer communications.  
If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information  
We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:   
We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, referrer URL, location, and the time zone where an Filetut product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.  
We may collect information regarding customer activities on our website, iCloud services, and iTunes Store and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.  
We may collect and store details of how you use our services, including search queries. This information may be used to improve the relevancy of results provided by our services. Except in limited instances to ensure quality of our services over the Internet, such information will not be associated with your IP address.  
With your explicit consent, we may collect data about how you use your device and applications in order to help app developers improve their apps.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.  
Cookies and Other Technologies

Filetut’s websites, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Filetut and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with Filetut more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you the next time you visit the Filetut Online Store. Knowing your country and language − and if you are an educator, your school − helps us provide a customized and more useful shopping experience. Knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain product or used a particular service helps us make our advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests. And knowing your contact information, hardware identifiers, and information about your computer or device helps us personalize your operating system, set up your iCloud service, and provide you with better customer service.

If you want to disable cookies and you’re using the Safari web browser, go to Safari preferences and then to the privacy pane to disable cookies. On your Filetut mobile device, go to Settings, then Safari, and then to the Cookies section. For other browsers, check with your provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the Filetut website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most internet services, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit websites and applications, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, to improve our product and services, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Filetut may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Filetut website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

Disclosure to Third Parties

At times Filetut may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Filetut to provide products and services, or that help Filetut market to customers. For example, when you purchase and activate your iPhone, you authorize Filetut and your carrier to exchange the information you provide during the activation process to carry out service. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by Filetut and your carrier’s respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by Filetut to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. Service Providers

Filetut shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever Filetut operates.

Others

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Filetut to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

Protection of Personal Information

Filetut takes the security of your personal information very seriously. Filetut online services such as the Filetut Online Store and iTunes Store protect your personal information during transit using encryption such as Transport Layer Security (TLS). When your personal data is stored by Filetut, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures. iCloud data is stored in encrypted form including when we utilize third party storage.

When you use some Filetut products, services, or applications or post on an Filetut forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information and content you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to share or submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

Filetut makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Access to Personal Information

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at https://Filetutid.asmfile.com/. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with access for any purpose including to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Filetut is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made through the regional Privacy Contact Form. Children

We understand the importance of taking extra precautions to protect the privacy and safety of children using Filetut products and services. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, without first receiving verifiable parental consent we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

Children under the age of 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, are not permitted to create their own Filetut IDs, unless their parent provided consent through the Filetut ID for Students Program or as part of the child account creation process in Family Sharing. For example, a parent must review the Filetut ID and Family Sharing Disclosure and agree to the Consent to Filetut’s Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Child’s Information; and the iTunes Store Terms and Conditions, before they can begin the Filetut ID account creation process for their child. Learn more about Family Sharing, the Filetut ID for Students program and Restrictions for children’s accounts.

If at any time a parent needs to access, correct, or delete data associated with their Family Sharing account or child’s Filetut ID, they may contact us through our Privacy Contact Form.

Or by using the contact information here.

Privacy Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about Filetut’s Privacy Policy or data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please contact us. You can always contact us by phone at the relevant Filetut Support number for your country.

All such communications are examined and replies issued where appropriate as soon as possible. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received, you may refer your complaint to the relevant regulator in your jurisdiction. If you ask us, we will endeavor to provide you with information about relevant complaint avenues which may be applicable to your circumstances.

Filetut may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
